[
  {
    "question": "In Anime Jujutsu Kaisen, How many seconds does Gojo ask to have with Itadori's 'Sukuna' form?'",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "15",
      "20",
      "30"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Jujutsu Kaisen, What type of weapon does Nobara use to exorcise curses?",
    "options": [
      "Hammer",
      "Sword",
      "Spear"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Hammer"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Jujutsu Kaisen, What task taught Itadori to control his emotions while using cursed energy to keep a doll asleep?",
    "options": [
      "Listening to Music",
      "Fight training",
      "Watching movies"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Watching movies"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Jujutsu Kaisen, Who is Gojo fighting when he teaches Itadori about domain expansion?",
    "options": [
      "Mahito",
      "Jogo",
      "Suguru Geto"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Jogo"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Jujutsu Kaisen, Where did Itadori and Nanami investigate the massacre by Mahito?",
    "options": [
      "A Mall",
      "A Movie Theatre",
      "A Grocery Store"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "A Movie Theatre"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Jujutsu Kaisen, Who is the character that Mahito kills to enrage Yuji?",
    "options": [
      "Nanami",
      "Junpei",
      "Megumi"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Junpei"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Jujutsu Kaisen, Who is the rival school to Tokyo's Jujutsu High?",
    "options": [
      "Kyoto Jujutsu High",
      "Osaka Jujutsu High",
      "Kobe Jujutsu High"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Kyoto Jujutsu High"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Jujutsu Kaisen, What question does Aoi Todo ask both Yuji and Megumi to see if they're boring?",
    "options": [
      "The type of food he likes",
      "The type of music he likes",
      "The type of women he likes"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "The type of women he likes"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Jujutsu Kaisen, What ability allows Aoi to switch places with Yuji by clapping his hands?",
    "options": [
      "Clap Back",
      "Trading Spaces",
      "Boogie Woogie"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Boogie Woogie"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Jujutsu Kaisen, What Straw Doll technique does Kugisaki use to keep Kechizu and Eso stunned?",
    "options": [
      "Resonance",
      "Hairpin",
      "Black Flash"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Resonance"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which PokÃƒÆ’Ã†â€™Ãƒâ€ Ã¢â‚¬â„¢ÃƒÆ’Ã¢â‚¬Å¡Ãƒâ€šÃ‚Â©mon has electricity-storing pouches on its cheeks?",
    "options": [
      "Pikachu",
      "Squirtle",
      "Gengar",
      "JigglyPuff"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Pikachu"
  },
  {
    "question": "What alien race battled the Robotech Defence Forces?",
    "options": [
      "Virm",
      "Ctarl",
      "Zentraedi",
      "saiyan"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Zentraedi"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which anime series tells the story of the counter-cyberterrorist organization Public Security Section 9?",
    "options": [
      "Darker than Black",
      "Paranoia Agent",
      "Neon Genesis Evangelion",
      " Ghost in the Shell"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Ghost in the Shell"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which anime series revolves around a boy who sells his soul to a demon?",
    "options": [
      "Black Butler",
      "Devilman",
      "Dragon Ball",
      " City Hunter"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Black Butler"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many Dragon Balls are there?",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "9",
      "8",
      "7"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which anime character was sold to the circus?",
    "options": [
      "Naruto",
      "Astro Boy",
      " Sailor Moon",
      " Black Jack"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Astro Boy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who protects the Silver Crystal?",
    "options": [
      "Captain Tsubasa",
      " Sailor Moon",
      " Black Jack",
      " Naruto"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Sailor Moon"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who solved the Millennium Puzzle?",
    "options": [
      "Seto Kaiba",
      " Joey Wheeler",
      " Yugi Mutou",
      " Bakura"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Yugi Mutou"
  },
  {
    "question": "Whose body gained the properties of rubber after unintentionally eating a Devil Fruit?",
    "options": [
      "Space Dandy",
      "BOBOBO-BO BO BOBO",
      "Don Patch",
      "Monkey D. Luffy"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Monkey D. Luffy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which anime series revolves around the Elric brothers?",
    "options": [
      "Crows",
      "Fullmetal Alchemist",
      "Berserk",
      "Glass Mask bro"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Fullmetal Alchemist"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which character in Cowboy Bebop is a genetically-engineered Pembroke Welsh Corgi with human-like intelligence?",
    "options": [
      "Spike",
      "Jet",
      "Vicious",
      "Ein"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Ein"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which anime series launched the musical career of Mari Iijima?",
    "options": [
      "Mobile Suit Gundam",
      "Super Dimension Fortress Macross",
      "Neon Genesis Evangelion",
      "Star Blazers"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Super Dimension Fortress Macross"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the navigator of the Straw Hat Pirates?",
    "options": [
      "Kaido",
      "Sabo",
      "Nami",
      "Shanks"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Nami"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is a member of an extraterrestrial warrior race called the Saiyans?",
    "options": [
      "Lady Armaroid",
      "Goku",
      "Naruto",
      "Zeref"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Goku"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which anime series follows a college student who rooms with a goddess in a Buddhist temple?",
    "options": [
      "The Godess Of Versailles",
      "Rookie Goddess",
      "My Sweet Goddess",
      " Oh My Goddess"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Oh My Goddess"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the longest running anime series?",
    "options": [
      "One Piece",
      "Sazae-san",
      "Prince Mackaroo",
      "Ojarumaru"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Sazae-san"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of Speed Racer's girlfriend?",
    "options": [
      "Trixie",
      "Nixie",
      "Dixie",
      "Pixie"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Trixie"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of Studio Ghibliâ€™s well-known mascot?",
    "options": [
      "Kiki",
      "Bakura",
      "Ponyo",
      "Totoro"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Totoro"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the first Hashira that Tanjiro met in the mountains?",
    "options": [
      "Giyu Tomioka",
      "Shinobu Kocho",
      "Tengen Uzui",
      "Zenitsu"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Giyu Tomioka"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of bird serves as a messenger to Demon Slayers?",
    "options": [
      "Hawks",
      "Eagles",
      "Pigeons",
      "Crows"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Crows"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of sword does a Demon Slayer wield?",
    "options": [
      "Steel Katana",
      "Nichirin Sword",
      "Adamantium Blade",
      "Black Blade"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Nichirin Sword"
  },
  {
    "question": "Name this trainer who taught Tanjiro his water breathing technique.",
    "options": [
      "Sankonji Urokodaki",
      "Kyojuro Rengoku",
      "Shinjiro Rengoku",
      "Peter Griffin"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Sankonji Urokodaki"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Demon Slayer, How many days did Tanjiro have to survive for the Final Selection?",
    "options": [
      "14",
      "5",
      "7",
      "9"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Demon Slayer, What is a demon's greatest weakness?",
    "options": [
      "Sunlight",
      "Water Breathing Technique",
      "Fire Breathing Technique",
      "Holy Water"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Sunlight"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Demon Slayer, Which Demon Slayer always gets Tanjiro's name wrong?",
    "options": [
      "Zenitsu Agatsuma",
      "Inosuke Hashibara",
      "Genya Shinazugawa",
      "Nezuko Kamado"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Inosuke Hashibara"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Demon Slayer, There are ___ Kizuki under Kibutsuji's command.",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "12",
      "14",
      "8"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Demon Slayer, What was the name of the drum demon who was removed from the Kizuki?",
    "options": [
      "Enmu",
      "Kyogai",
      "Akaza",
      "Ritsu"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Kyogai"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Demon Slayer, Who are the two demons on the run from Kibutsuji?",
    "options": [
      "Nezuko and Tanjiro",
      "Rui and Enmu",
      "Tamayo and Yushiro",
      "Zenitsu and Inosuke"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Tamayo and Yushiro"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Demon Slayer literally kills demons in his sleep?",
    "options": [
      "Zenitsu",
      "Inosuke",
      "Tanjiro",
      "Nezuko"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Zenitsu"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Demon Slayer, What did Tanjiro sell before he became a Demon Slayer?",
    "options": [
      "Iron ore",
      "Charcoal",
      "Lumber",
      "Wood"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Charcoal"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Demon Slayer, Which two Demon Slayers had never seen a train before?",
    "options": [
      "Zenitsu and Inosuke",
      "Inosuke and Tanjiro",
      "Tanjiro and Zenitsu",
      "Zenitsu and Nezuko"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Inosuke and Tanjiro"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which studio adapted Steins;Gate?",
    "options": [
      "White Fox",
      "Madhouse",
      "A-1 Pictures ",
      "Production I.G "
    ],
    "correct_answer": "White Fox"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which anime is Toei Animations known for the most?",
    "options": [
      "Dragon Ball",
      "Hunter x Hunter",
      "One Piece",
      "Detective Conan"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "One Piece"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which studio adapted Haikyuu?",
    "options": [
      "Production I.G",
      "Sunrise",
      "Bones",
      "J.C. Staff"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Production I.G"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which studio adapted the Monogatari Series?",
    "options": [
      "Shaft",
      "Ufotable",
      "Trigger",
      "Kyoto Animation"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Shaft"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which studio adapted Code Geass?",
    "options": [
      "Sunrise",
      "Bones",
      "Wit Studio",
      "Madhouse"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Sunrise"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which anime is not adapted by Wit Studio?",
    "options": [
      "Vinland Saga",
      "Great Pretender",
      "Seraph of the End",
      "Yuri on Ice!!!"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Yuri on Ice!!!"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which anime is not adapted by MAPPA?",
    "options": [
      "Terror in Resonance",
      "Yuri on Ice!!!",
      "Kids on the Slope",
      "Angel Beats"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Angel Beats"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which anime is not adapted by Kyoto Animation?",
    "options": [
      "Full Metal Panic",
      "The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya",
      "CLANNAD",
      "No Game No Life"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "No Game No Life"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which anime is not adapted by Studio Bones?",
    "options": [
      "Fullmetal Alchemist",
      "Attack on Titan",
      "Ouran High School Host Club",
      "My Hero Academia"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Attack on Titan"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one of these are not by Studio Ghibli?",
    "options": [
      "Spirited Away",
      "Princess Monoke",
      "Your Name",
      "My Neighbor Totoro"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Your Name"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which anime is not adapted by Production I.G?",
    "options": [
      "Ghost in The Shell",
      "Psycho-Pass",
      "Haikyu!!",
      "Log Horizon"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Log Horizon"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which anime is not adapted by CloverWorks?",
    "options": [
      "Black Clover",
      "Rascan Does Not Dream of Bunny Girl Senpai",
      "Wonder Egg Priority",
      "Promised Neverland"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Black Clover"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which anime is not adapted by Studio Pierrot?",
    "options": [
      "Tokyo Ghoul",
      "Naruto",
      "Bleach",
      "Fairy Tail"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Fairy Tail"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which anime is not adapted by A-1 Pictures?",
    "options": [
      "Your Lie In April",
      "Silver Spoon",
      "Saga of Tanya the Evil",
      "Sword Art Online"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Saga of Tanya the Evil"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which anime is not adapted by Toei Animation?",
    "options": [
      "Dragon Ball",
      "Sailor Moon",
      "Digimon",
      "Gate"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Gate"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which anime is not adapted by Trigger?",
    "options": [
      "Gurren Lagan",
      "DARLING in the FRANXX",
      "Little Wich Academia",
      "Isekai Cheat Magician"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Isekai Cheat Magician"
  },
  {
    "question": "Out of these which anime is adapted by P.A. Works?",
    "options": [
      "Charlotte",
      "KonoSuba",
      "Saiki. Kusuo",
      "Overlord"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Charlotte"
  },
  {
    "question": "Out of these which anime is adapted by J.C. Staff?",
    "options": [
      "Violet Evergarden",
      "One Punch Man",
      "Devil is a Part Timer",
      "Drifters"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "One Punch Man"
  },
  {
    "question": "Out of these which anime is adapted by Shaft?",
    "options": [
      "Alita Battle Angel",
      "March Comes in Like A Lion",
      "Evangelion",
      "Tower of God"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "March Comes in Like A Lion"
  },
  {
    "question": "Out of these which anime is adapted by Gainax?",
    "options": [
      "FLCL",
      "Ghost Stories",
      "Berserk",
      "Monster"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "FLCL"
  },
  {
    "question": "Out of these which anime is adapted by Brain's Base?",
    "options": [
      "SNAFU",
      "Noragami",
      "Bungou Stray Dogs",
      "Banana Fish"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "SNAFU"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who voiced Natsuki Subaru in the anime Re:Zero?",
    "options": [
      "Kobayashi Yusuke",
      "Mamoru Miyano",
      "Yuki Kaji",
      "Hiroshi Kamiya"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Kobayashi Miyano"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sophie is a character from which anime movie? ",
    "options": [
      "Go! Princess PreCure ",
      "Snow White WIth The Red Hair ",
      "Howl's Moving Castle ",
      "Sailor Moon "
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Howl's Moving Castle"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Dragon Ball Super, Goku is sent to destroy earth. What happened to make him change his ways?",
    "options": [
      "He just realised it was quite mean",
      "He bumped his head",
      "He couldn't be bothered in the end",
      "No-one knows"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "He bumped his head"
  },
  {
    "question": "a boy has his family murdered and then joins the fire department seeking revenge. Guess the anime from the bad description ",
    "options": [
      "Tokyo Revengers ",
      "Demon Slayer ",
      "Fire Force ",
      "Naruto"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Fire Force"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the original creator of the Rasengan? ",
    "options": [
      "Jiraiya ",
      "Minato ",
      "Naruto ",
      "Tobirama"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Minato"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is known as the \"God of Shinobi\"? ",
    "options": [
      "Hashirama ",
      "Hiruzen ",
      "Kaguya ",
      "Madara"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Hashirama"
  },
  {
    "question": "How old does Naruto turn at the end of the 4th Great Shinobi War? ",
    "options": [
      "15 ",
      "16 ",
      "17 ",
      "18 "
    ],
    "correct_answer": "17"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was not a part of the Sasuke Retrieval squad? ",
    "options": [
      "Choji ",
      "Kiba ",
      "Neji ",
      "Shino"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Shino"
  },
  {
    "question": "What chakra nature does Naruto use? ",
    "options": [
      "Earth ",
      "Fire ",
      "Lightning ",
      "Wind"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Wind"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does Shippuden mean in \"Naruto Shippuden\"? ",
    "options": [
      "Hurricane ",
      "Storm ",
      "Tornado ",
      "Tsunami "
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Hurricane"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many members are in the Akatsuki at the beginning of Naruto Shippuden? ",
    "options": [
      "8 ",
      "9 ",
      "10 ",
      "11"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is responsible for the death of Obito? ",
    "options": [
      "Kaguya ",
      "Kakashi ",
      "Madara ",
      "Naruto"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Kaguya"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which clan is known for their use of insects?",
    "options": [
      "Aburame Clan",
      "Inuzuka Clan",
      "Nara Clan",
      "Yamanaka Clan"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Aburame Clan"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the position that rules the Hidden Mist Village? ",
    "options": [
      "Kazekage ",
      "Mizukage ",
      "Raikage ",
      "Tsuchikage"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Mizukage"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many of Kurama's cloaked tails emerged during Naruto's fight against Orochimaru? ",
    "options": [
      "1 ",
      "2 ",
      "3 ",
      "4"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was Kushina's nickname?",
    "options": [
      "Red Devil of the Leaf",
      "Red Hot Habanero",
      "Red Hot Chili Pepper",
      "Red Headed Devil"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Red Hot Habanero"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one of these is NOT a Mangekyo ability? ",
    "options": [
      "Amaterasu ",
      "Kamui ",
      "Kotoamatsukami ",
      "Tenseigan "
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Tenseigan"
  },
  {
    "question": "What year did the first adaptation of fruits basket air? ",
    "options": [
      "2002 ",
      "2001 ",
      "2000 ",
      "1999 "
    ],
    "correct_answer": "2001"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Mikitaka's real name? ",
    "options": [
      "Mioka Natakashi Dow ",
      "Wapera Mikitaka Eka ",
      "Azawana Miki Mei ",
      "Nu Mikitakazo Nshi"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Nu Mikitakazo Nshi"
  },
  {
    "question": "In JJBA:P4, What is Mikitaka's real name? ",
    "options": [
      "Mioka Natakashi Dow ",
      "Wapera Mikitaka Eka ",
      "Azawana Miki Mei ",
      "Nu Mikitakazo Nshi "
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Nu Mikitakazo Nshi"
  },
  {
    "question": "How did Kakyoin attack Jotaro when he was first revealed?",
    "options": [
      "Paintbrush ",
      "Gun ",
      "Katana ",
      "His Stand"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "His Stand"
  },
  {
    "question": "In JJBA:P4, What is the name of Yukako's Stand?",
    "options": [
      "Heart",
      "Quiet Riot",
      "Love Deluxe",
      "Poison"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Poison"
  },
  {
    "question": "In JJBA:P4, What is the name of Yukako's Stand? ",
    "options": [
      "Heart ",
      "Quiet Riot ",
      "Love Deluxe ",
      "Poison "
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Love Deluxe"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who did Diavolo switch bodies with during the Chariot Requiem Arc? ",
    "options": [
      "Mista ",
      "Narancia ",
      "Bruno ",
      "Trish"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Bruno"
  },
  {
    "question": "How old was Jonathan at the beginning of Phantom Blood? ",
    "options": [
      "12 ",
      "15 ",
      "10 ",
      "18"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Lisa Lisa's real name? ",
    "options": [
      "Elizabeth ",
      "Annabel ",
      "Jannet ",
      "Suzie"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Elizabeth"
  },
  {
    "question": "In JJBA:P5, What was the first thing Doppio used as a phone to call Diavalo?",
    "options": [
      "A phone",
      "A cigarette",
      "A frog",
      "A car ornament"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "A phone"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the vampire seen during the beginning of Battle Tendency? ",
    "options": [
      "Straizo ",
      "Buford ",
      "Dio ",
      "Donovin"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Straizo"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of Norisuke Higashikata's Stand?",
    "options": [
      "Paper Moon King",
      "King Nothing",
      "Paisley Park",
      "Doobie Wah!"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "King Nothing"
  },
  {
    "question": "What city did Ghiaccio rant about? ",
    "options": [
      "Paris ",
      "Rome ",
      "Naples ",
      "Venice"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Venice"
  },
  {
    "question": "At what time did Funny Valentine shoot Johnny Joestar?",
    "options": [
      "3:35 PM",
      "4:04 PM",
      "4:08 PM",
      "4:12 PM"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "4:08 PM"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Joestar ended the bloodline?",
    "options": [
      "Jotaro",
      "Josuke",
      "Jolyne",
      "Johnny"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Jolyne"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who helped Koichi learn fluent Italian in Golden Wind?",
    "options": [
      "Jotaro",
      "Rohan",
      "Josuke",
      "Yuya"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Rohan"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the Ending theme of Part 4 Diamond Is Unbreakable?",
    "options": [
      "I Want You",
      "Face Off",
      "Free Bird",
      "Everybody Wants To Rule The World"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "I Want You"
  },
  {
    "question": "In JJBA:P4, Who is the host of Morioh Radio?",
    "options": [
      "Yuya Fungami",
      "Kai Harada",
      "Terunosuke Miyamoto",
      "Tamami Kobayashi"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Kai Harada"
  },
  {
    "question": "In JJBA, What does Kakyoin mention is his favorite musician?",
    "options": [
      "Led Zeppelin",
      "Pearl Jam",
      "Guns N' Roses",
      "Sting"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Sting"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kanji does Yoshikage Kira bite into his nails?",
    "options": [
      "Luck",
      "Peace",
      "Hope",
      "Terror"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Luck"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Araki's favorite JoJo?",
    "options": [
      "Jotaro",
      "Josuke 4",
      "Jonathan",
      "Josuke 8"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Josuke 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many people tackled Jonathan before he had to throw the ball to Dio during their Rugby game?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "4",
      "2",
      "6"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "In JJBA P5, What is Doppio's first name?",
    "options": [
      "Vinegar",
      "Polenta",
      "Pizza",
      "Ossobuco"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Vinegar"
  },
  {
    "question": "In JJBA P4, What is the name of Killer Queens' first bomb?",
    "options": [
      "Sheer Heart Attack",
      "Killer Queen Bites The Dust",
      "Bomb Transmutation",
      "Break Free"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Bomb Transmutation"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who are the 2 illegitimate members of the Joestar Bloodline?",
    "options": [
      "Jolyne and Giorno",
      "Giorno and Josuke",
      "Josuke and Jolyne",
      "Jolyne and DIO"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Giorno and Josuke"
  },
  {
    "question": "How much of Josuke's money did Joseph spend on baby supplies?",
    "options": [
      "120,000 Yen",
      "150,000 Yen",
      "190,000 Yen",
      "130,000 Yen"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "130,000 Yen"
  },
  {
    "question": "How old is Josuke in part 8 Jojolion?",
    "options": [
      "16",
      "15",
      "19",
      "22"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "19"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which quintessentially Japanese dish originates from Portugal?",
    "options": [
      "Sushi",
      "Ramen",
      "Takoyaki",
      "Tempura"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Tempura"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these car manufacturers is not Japanese?",
    "options": [
      "Daihatsu",
      "Lexus",
      "Hyundai",
      "Nissan"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Hyundai"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is the longest running anime series?",
    "options": [
      "One Piece",
      "YU-GI-OH",
      "Detective Conan",
      "Crayon Shin-Chan"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Crayon Shin-Chan"
  },
  {
    "question": "Japan turns which of the following into renewable energy?",
    "options": [
      "Stationary Bikes",
      "Leftover Sushi Rice",
      "Footsteps",
      "Crowd Noises"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Footsteps"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the second largest city in Japan by Population?",
    "options": [
      "Yokohama",
      "Osaka",
      "Nagoya",
      "Kyoto"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Yokohama"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many siblings does Killua Zoldyck have?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "4",
      "5",
      "2"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "When was the first time Killua & Gon met?",
    "options": [
      "Hunter Exam",
      "Heavens Arena",
      "Greed Island",
      "Whale Tail Island"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Hunter Exam"
  },
  {
    "question": "How old is Hisoka? ",
    "options": [
      "12 ",
      "30 ",
      "28",
      "44"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "28"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many points has Hisoka won against Gon at Heavens Arena?",
    "options": [
      "10-6",
      "9-4",
      "2-1",
      "3-4"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "9-4"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why does Kurapika hate spiders?",
    "options": [
      "because they are creepy",
      "because they remind him of the Phantom Troupe",
      "because they murdered his parents",
      "because he has Arachnophobia "
    ],
    "correct_answer": "because they remind him of the Phantom Troupe"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why does Gon want to become a Hunter?",
    "options": [
      "Because of his dad",
      "Because he was forced to",
      "Because he wants to make new friends",
      "Because he wants to go on an adventure"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Because of his dad"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many Phantom Troupe members are there?",
    "options": [
      "44",
      "13",
      "16",
      "20"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "13"
  },
  {
    "question": "What Nen does Illumi have?",
    "options": [
      "Transmutation",
      "Specialization",
      "Manipulation",
      "Emuter"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Manipulation"
  }
]